{
    "id": "357a0a326a9f456b96fe1b6636555afb",
    "title": "Intermediate Vocabulary Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "It is very difficult to give ……………………….. criticism.",
            "description": "Objective criticism means impartial criticism.",
            "answers": [
                "objective",
                "object",
                "objectionable"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e84ef3a1c23547e3beb96b9c6fd2d6f1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Paying taxes is …………………………..",
            "description": "If something is obligatory, it is compulsory.",
            "answers": [
                "obligation",
                "obligatory",
                "obliging"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ccb19f5c469747dc846417a75b7b6080"
        },
        {
            "question": "How can you be so ………………………. to her rude remarks?",
            "description": "If you are oblivious to something, you are unmindful of it.",
            "answers": [
                "oblique",
                "oblivion",
                "oblivious"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "fe77f4d4769c4794ae0a2a9c6f3efdf3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Don’t be so ……………………….. in other people’s affairs.",
            "description": "Obtrusive means interfering or meddling.",
            "answers": [
                "obstructive",
                "obtrusive",
                "objective"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dc46b48d502a454485a0d43a70451482"
        },
        {
            "question": "The weather was good except for an ………………………… shower.",
            "description": "Occasional means taking place from time to time.",
            "answers": [
                "occasion",
                "occasional",
                "occasionally"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "616e31de7baa414cb2efdf5ab6dd26db"
        },
        {
            "question": "An egg with two yolks is an ………………………..",
            "description": "Oddity means rarity.",
            "answers": [
                "odd",
                "oddity",
                "odds"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "91523e055da941d48251327c8d99c6f4"
        },
        {
            "question": "The peoples of the two countries must learn to understand …………………………",
            "description": "One another applies to more than two people while each other applies to only two people.",
            "answers": [
                "one another",
                "each other"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b5c702f629b44f14b98f66a3e62e6d5b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The army’s ……………………… march continued.",
            "description": "Onwards can only be an adverb. Onward is always correct as an adjective or an adverb.",
            "answers": [
                "onward",
                "onwards",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "feeb15b8fe2d4d9ab55ff9cd5dc74196"
        },
        {
            "question": "Now would be an ………………………….. time to buy a new book.",
            "description": "Opportune means favourable or advantageous.",
            "answers": [
                "opportunity",
                "opportune",
                "opportunistic"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bccd7903c3a943769b232d430f30d3c1"
        },
        {
            "question": "The experiment was conducted under ………………………….. conditions.",
            "description": "Optimum means ideal or perfect. Optimal means the same.",
            "answers": [
                "optimum",
                "optimal",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5a46e1803c58447fb989c1d97e7188cf"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following phrases mean in good faith?",
            "description": "Bona fide means in good faith.",
            "answers": [
                "bona fide",
                "ex gratia",
                "sine qua non"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "03a8a1211f6045e5995948829cca4295"
        },
        {
            "question": "The Ohio river forms the boundary …………………………. Kentucky and Indiana.",
            "description": "To speak of two distinct objects we use between.",
            "answers": [
                "among",
                "between"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "38cc18e7a2804eca8dcc91e5241675ef"
        }
    ]
}